Guide to the United Student Christian Council Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Denominational and YMCA Correspondence and Publications, Series VIII
  - Publications and Printed Materials
    - NICC, Minutes of Social Responsibility Committee, 1948-1949 (Box 140, Folder 1616)
    - NICC, Newsletters, Actions: National Assembly of the Student Christian Association Movement and Student Public Affairs News, 1946-1948 (Box 141, Folder 1617)
    - NICC, Program pamphlets, What Christian Associations Can do Toward Christian Faith by Fern Babcock, What Christian Associations Can do Toward Full Employment by Edmonia Grant, and What Student Christian Associations Can do Toward World Organization by Paul Limbert and Fern Babcock, 1946-1947 (Box 141, Folder 1618)
    - NICC, Program papers including Preparing New Leaders for Student YMCA's, YWCA's and CA's by Fern Babcock, Toward World Understanding on the Campus by Fern Babcock, Economic Justice by Clara A. Hardin and Fern Babcock, and Civil Liberties on Campus by Leila Anderson, Ray Gibbons, and George T. Parker, 1947-1949, 1951 (Box 141, Folder 1619)
    - NICC, Study guides including World Study Guide for World Relatedness Commissions in Student YMCA's, YWCA's, and CA's, 1950 (Box 141, Folder 1620)
    - NICC, Summer programs information, 1949-1952 (Box 141, Folder 1621)
    - National Student Council of the YMCA-YWCA, Annual Assembly materials, 1947-1959 (Box 141, Folder 1622)
    - NSCY, Booklets You in the University, The Inescapable Question: Where are You? by Howard Clark Kee, You the Nation and the World by Ernest W. Lefever and Herman F. Reissig, and Faith, Sex and Love by William Hamilton, 1954-1955 (Box 141, Folder 1623)
    - NSCY, Brochures, n.d. (Box 141, Folder 1624)
    - NSCY, Memo re. Political responsibility, minutes of the administrative committee, and periodical Intercollegian, 1953, 1959 (Box 141, Folder 1625)
    - NSCY, Pamphlet, papers, and reports including The New Frontier for the Student YMCA and YWCA by A.L. Kershaw, "The Meaning of Life Derived from the Campus," and Reports: NSCY 1956 Work Groups, 1955-1957 (Box 141, Folder 1626)
    - NSCY, Workbook for student delegates newly elected to the NSCY, 1957 (Box 141, Folder 1627)
    - Northern Baptist, Brochures and directories, 1947-1948 (Box 141, Folder 1628)
    - Northern Baptist, A Manual for Pastor and Adult Advisors of Students in Baptist Churches in College Communities and The Student Counselor on the Job: a Handbook for Student Counselors, 1949-1952 (Box 141, Folder 1629)
    - Northern Baptist, The Northern Baptist Student Newsletter continued as The American Baptist Student Newsletter, 1949-1952 (Box 142, Folder 1630)
    - Northern Baptist, Newsletters from regional groups including Green Laker and Student Times: a Publication by and for the Students of Ohio, 1948-1950 (Box 142, Folder 1631)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S., Brochures, 1953-1958 (Box 142, Folder 1632)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S., College prep materials, Going to College Handbook and paper "College Days and Christian Ways or Christian Student, Beware or so You're Going to College? or Christian Ways for college Days" by Harry Gordon Goodykoontz (Box 142, Folder 1633)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S., Minutes of the Thirty-Fourth Annual Meeting of the Presbyterian Educational Association of the South, 1948 (Box 142, Folder 1634)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S., Newsletter, Campus Christian Life News, 1955-1957 (Box 142, Folder 1635)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S., Newsletter, Campus Christian Life News, 1957-1959 (Box 142, Folder 1636)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S., Newsletter, miscellaneous regional groups including The Newsletter: Greater Atlanta Presbyterian Student News and The Fellowship, 1952-1956 (Box 142, Folder 1637)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S., Newsletter, The Presbyterian Student, 1950-1952 (Box 142, Folder 1638)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S., Newsletter, The Presbyterian Student, 1952-1955 (Box 143, Folder 1639)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S., Pamphlets including Westminster Fellowship Program Emphasis, The Two Shall be One: a Christian Understanding of Sex by Albert C. Wynn, and Thy Will--My Will: a Guide for Personal Devotions, 1950-1956 (Box 143, Folder 1640)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S., Workbook for Westminster Fellowships prepared by the Department of Campus Christian Life of the Presbyterian Church U.S., 1954-1955 (Box 143, Folder 1641)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A., Circular letter: Student Work Communique, 1949-1950 (Box 143, Folder 1642)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A., Circular letter: Student Work Communique, 1952-1955 (Box 143, Folder 1643)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A., Materials for Association of Presbyterian University Pastors including article by Arnold Nash The Totalitarian University and Christian Higher Education, booklet Westminster Fellowship Comes to First Church, study pamphlets, and miscellaneous brochures, 1950 (Box 143, Folder 1644)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A., Minutes and reports from the Association of Presbyterian University Pastors, 1952-1952 (Box 143, Folder 1645)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A., Minutes and reports from the Association of Presbyterian University Pastors, 1955-1956 (Box 143, Folder 1646)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A., Minutes and reports from the Association of Presbyterian University Pastors, 1957-1958 (Box 144, Folder 1647)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A., Newsletters, The Westminster Fellowship Student Reporter and The Wee Kirk, 1954-1955, 1958 (Box 144, Folder 1648)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A., Pamphlets including Decision in Retrospect by Mary Genevieve Lewis, Perspective on Student Work: a Report on Westminster Foundation Work on University Campuses, and Principles Policies and Procedures of the Student Work of the Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A., 1946-1954 (Box 144, Folder 1649)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A., Periodical Social Progress, 1958-1959 (Box 144, Folder 1650)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A., Program materials for summer service projects, 1952-1954 (Box 144, Folder 1651)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A., Reports from foreign missions and book New Day Dawning by William Richey Hogg, 1957-1958 (Box 144, Folder 1652)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A., Reports from Westminster Fellowship National Council and the Presbyterian Student work survey, 1952 (Box 144, Folder 1653)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A., Study materials from Westminster Fellowship at UNC, n.d. (Box 144, Folder 1654)
    - Protestant Episcopal, Booklets, The Field of the Cloth of Gold by Reverend Thomas van B. Barrett, Handbook for College Workers, and Theological Studies & Examinations: a Syllabus, 1948, 1952, n.d. (Box 144, Folder 1655)
    - Protestant Episcopal, Brochures, circa 1947-1956 (Box 145, Folder 1656)
    - Protestant Episcopal, Conference materials, 1955 (Box 145, Folder 1657)
    - Protestant Episcopal, Constitution of the National Canterbury Association of the Protestant Episcopal Church in the United States of America, n.d. (Box 145, Folder 1658)
    - Protestant Episcopal, Newsletter, The Church on the Campus, 1954 (Box 145, Folder 1659)
    - Protestant Episcopal, Newsletter, Church Review News and Faculty Notes, 1953-1959 (Box 145, Folder 1660)
    - Protestant Episcopal, Newsletter, miscellaneous, 1947-1949, 1959 (Box 145, Folder 1661)
    - Protestant Episcopal, Newsletter, The National Canterburian, 1955 (Box 145, Folder 1662)
    - Protestant Episcopal, National Canterbury Association Newsletter, 1950 (Box 145, Folder 1663)
    - Protestant Episcopal, National Canterbury Association Newsletter, 1951-1952 (Box 145, Folder 1664)
    - Protestant Episcopal, Reports from conferences, 1949, 1950 (Box 145, Folder 1665)
    - Protestant Episcopal, Summer programs, 1948-1949 (Box 145, Folder 1666)
    - Protestant Episcopal, Untitled handbook on work with college students (Box 145, Folder 1667)
    - United Student Fellowship, Brochures, n.d. (Box 145, Folder 1668)
    - USF, Conference materials from the United Student Assembly conference including group photograph and 1958 summer conferences, June 14-18, 1948, 1958 (Box 145, Folder 1669)
    - USF, News-Letter of the United Student Fellowship, 1948-1951 (Box 146, Folder 1670)
    - USF, Newsletter, Resource includes brochures and flyers, 1954-1955 (Box 146, Folder 1671)
    - USF, Newsletter, Resource includes brochures and flyers, 1956 (Box 146, Folder 1672)
    - USF, Newsletter, Resource includes brochures and flyers, 1957 (Box 146, Folder 1673)
    - USF, Newsletter, Resource includes brochures and flyers, 1957-1958 (Box 146, Folder 1674)
    - USF, Newsletter, Resource includes brochures and flyers, 1958-1959 (Box 146, Folder 1675)
    - USF, Pamphlet, Rediscovering the Church: a Study Guide for Lesslie Newbigin's book The Household of God by Eugene S. Wehrli, 1955 (Box 146, Folder 1676)
    - USF, Periodical, Encounter, 1955-1958 (Box 146, Folder 1677)
    - USF, Reports on various conferences and USF student groups, 1951, 1954 (Box 146, Folder 1678)
    - YMCA, Booklets, City YMCAs and Student Work, The Religion of College Teachers by R.H. Edwin Espy, and The University, the Church and the YMCA by Bruce B. Maguire, 1950, 1957 (Box 146, Folder 1679)
    - YMCA, Brochures, flyers, and program materials from college and university YMCAs, 1949, 1950 (Box 146, Folder 1680)
    - YMCA, Cambell Commission, 1948-1949 (Box 147, Folder 1681)
    - YMCA, Campbell Commission, 1949-1950 (Box 147, Folder 1682)
    - YMCA, Flyers, n.d. (Box 147, Folder 1683)
    - YMCA, Meeting agenda and materials from National Advisory Council of the YMCA and minutes of the annual meeting of the National Student Council of the YMCA, 1952 (Box 147, Folder 1684)
    - YMCA, National Council Bulletin: a Service of Information, Interpretation, and Leadership for Member Associations and Pacific Northwest Newsletter: Student YMCA-YWCA Councils, 1955, 1957 (Box 147, Folder 1685)
    - YMCA, Periodical, De Unges Blad and Student World, 1950, 1951 (Box 147, Folder 1686)
    - YMCA, Proceedings of Conference on Campus Marriage and program booklet from 75th anniversary of YMCA of the University of Illinois, 1948, 1949 (Box 147, Folder 1687)
    - YMCA, Program materials for regional groups, 1956-1959 (Box 147, Folder 1688)
    - YMCA, Report of the President to the Board of Trustees of National Board of Young Men's Christian Associations, 1949, 1957 (Box 147, Folder 1689)
    - YWCA, Periodical, Public Affairs News Service include news paper clipping re. YWCA and Communist allegations, 1944, n.d. (Box 147, Folder 1690)
    - YWCA, Program Packet: New Dimensions of Memberships and Kit for National Student Council YWCA, 1950, 1951 (Box 147, Folder 1691)
    - YWCA, Reports, 1953 Annual Report: The YWCA in a Scientific Age, 1954 Annual Report: The YWCA and Woman Today, and The YWCA Reports for the Year 1956, 1953, 1954, 1956 (Box 147, Folder 1692)
- Related Organizations, Series IX
  - Chinese Student Christian Association
    - Constitution of the Chinese Students Christian Association and the CSCA and CFR Relationship (Box 108, Folder #1265)
    - Correspondence, re. Chinese Student Christian Association becoming a related movement to the USCC includes minutes from Committee on Friendly Relations Among Foreign Students, CSCA, and USCC, 1946-1949 (Box 108, Folder 1266)
    - Correspondence, re. Chinese Student Christian Association becoming a related movement to the USCC, 1949-1950 (Box 108, Folder 1267)
    - Correspondence, between Charles Hein (USCC-WSCF chairman) and Siu May Ting (secretary of CSCA, 1949-1950 (Box 108, Folder 1268)
    - Correspondence, re. Chinese students facing deportation includes news clippings and meeting minutes, 1950-1951 (Box 108, Folder 1269)
    - Minutes of the Advisory Council includes memos, 1949-1950 (Box 108, Folder 1270)
    - Printed materials, brochure and newsletters Here and There in C.S.C.A. and The Witness vol. xxxii, no. 28, 1949-1950 (Box 108, Folder 1271)
    - Reports, Annual reports, Report on the Situation of C.S.C.A. on the West Coast by Siu May Ting, and WSCF report: The Situation of the Chinese Students' Christian Association in North America by K.H. Ting, 1949-1950 (Box 108, Folder 1272)
  - Committee on Friendly Relations Among Foreign Students
    - Consultation between Committee on Friendly Relations Among Foreign Student and National Council of Churches of Christ in the U.S.A., 1958 (Box 108, Folder 1273)
    - Correspondence, General, 1946-1949 (Box 108, Folder 1274)
    - Correspondence, General, 1950-1952 (Box 109, Folder 1275)
    - Correspondence, re. Publication International Students and the Church, 1953-1954 (Box 109, Folder 1276)
    - Correspondence, re. Development of work with international students, 1954-1956 (Box 109, Folder 1277)
    - Correspondence, General, 1954-1959 (Box 109, Folder 1278)
    - Correspondence, re. international student attendance at conferences, 1955 (Box 109, Folder 1279)
    - Minutes, 1947-1948 (Box 109, Folder 1280)
    - Minutes, 1949-1950 (Box 109, Folder 1281)
    - Minutes, 1950-1951 (Box 109, Folder 1282)
    - Minutes, 1951-1952 (Box 109, Folder 1283)
    - Minutes, 1954-1956 (Box 109, Folder 1284)
    - Minutes, 1957-1958 (Box 109, Folder 1285)
    - Publications, Brochures, circa 1947-1959 (Box 110, Folder 1286)
    - Publications, Newsletters including Students from Other Lands: News and Information from the Committee on Friendly Relations Among Foreign Students, 1946-1956 (Box 110, Folder 1287)
    - Publications, Papers including "One World in Our Front Yard: What Students from Abroad Mean for our Local Communities" and International Campus, 1950, 1946, 1950 (Box 110, Folder 1288)
    - Publications, Pamphlets Education for One World, International Students and the Church, International Students Campus...Community, Living in the United States: a Guide for New Visitors, and Unofficial Ambassadors in the Community, 1946-1956 (Box 110, Folder 1289)
    - Publications, Pamphlets Summer with a Purpose and Ventures for International Students Interested in Travel, circa 1954-1958 (Box 110, Folder 1290)
    - Publications, Periodical, The Unofficial Ambassadors, 1948-1949, 1952, 1956 (Box 110, Folder 1291)
    - Summary report of west coast trip by Ruth Haines Purkaple, February 17-March 9, 1959 (Box 110, Folder 1292)
  - Interseminary Movement
    - Conference materials for the North American Interseminary Conference including notes of John Deschner, June 11-18, 1947 (Box 110, Folder 1293)
    - Correspondence, General, 1945-1949 (Box 110, Folder 1294)
    - Correspondence, General, 1950-1952 (Box 110, Folder 1295)
    - Minutes, 1946, 1947, 1950-1951 (Box 110, Folder 1296)
    - Printed materials, including newsletter National Interseminary News and The Sixteenth Biennial Meeting of the American Association of Theological Schools, 1948-1949 (Box 110, Folder 1297)
  - National Council of Churches of Christ in the United States of America
    - NCCC Proposed Merger with the USCC
      - Circular letters re. merger, 1950-1952 (Box 110, Folder 1298)
      - Consultation on NCCC, USCC, and the Future of the sCm, September 1951 (Box 110, Folder 1299)
      - Correspondence, re. NCCC negotiations, 1948-1950 (Box 111, Folder 1300)
      - Correspondence, re. NCCC negotiations, 1950-1951 (Box 111, Folder 1301)
      - Correspondence, re. NCCC negotiations, 1951 (Box 111, Folder 1302)
      - Correspondence, re. NCCC negotiations, 1951-1952 (Box 111, Folder 1303)
      - Letter from John Deschner to USCC re. NCCC merger (Deschner wrote this letter after his resignation as executive secretary), September 27-October 16, 1952 (Box 111, Folder 1304)
      - Member Movement reactions to USCC-NCCC merger, 1951-1952 (Box 111, Folder 1305)
      - Memo, re. Consultation on NCCCUSA's Department of Campus Christian Life, January 24, 1953 (Box 111, Folder 1306)
      - Proposal, "The United Student Christian Council and the National Council of Churches: the Proposal that USCC Should Operate as a Department of NCCC includes drafts, 1951 (Box 111, Folder 1307)
      - Reports, 1951-1952 (Box 111, Folder 1308)
    - NCCC General records
      - Annual Meeting of Department of Christian Education, 1954, 1955 (Box 112, Folder 1309)
      - By laws and The Closer Relationships of General Interdenominational Agencies: Report of Committee on Further Procedure, 1944 (Box 112, Folder 1310)
      - Correspondence, General, 1949-1952 (Box 112, Folder 1311)
      - Correspondence, Commission on Christian Higher Education, 1951-1952 (Box 112, Folder 1312)
      - Correspondence, Department of Campus Christian Life, 1951 (Box 112, Folder 1313)
      - Correspondence, Department of Evangelism, 1951 (Box 112, Folder 1314)
      - Correspondence, Department of Evangelism--Literature Committee, 1951 (Box 112, Folder 1315)
      - Correspondence, Ecumenical Work Camps Committee, 1951 (Box 112, Folder 1316)
      - Correspondence, Department of International Justice and Goodwill, 1952 (Box 112, Folder 1317)
      - Correspondence, Department of Pastoral Services, 1952 (Box 112, Folder 1318)
      - Memos, Joint Department of Religious Liberty, 1951 (Box 112, Folder 1319)
      - Memos, General, 1956-1959 (Box 112, Folder 1320)
      - Minutes, Department of Campus Christian Life--Strategy and Projects Committee, 1954 (Box 112, Folder 1321)
      - Minutes, Department of Campus Christian Life--Strategy and Projects Committee, 1954-1955 (Box 112, Folder 1322)
      - Minutes, General Board, 1954 (Box 113, Folder 1323)
      - Minutes, General Board, 1954-1955 (Box 113, Folder 1324)
      - Portfolio of materials for the constituting convention of the National Council of the Churches of Christ in the United States of America, 1950 (Box 113, Folder 1325)
      - Proposed budget asking from denominational relief agencies for Department of Church World Service and related organizations, 1952 (Box 113, Folder 1326)
      - Reports, 1951, 1957-1958 (Box 113, Folder 1327)
    - NCCC Publications and Printed Materials
      - Booklet, 1953 Yearbook: Division of Christian Education (Box 113, Folder 1328)
      - Booklet, 1954 Yearbook: Division of Christian Education (Box 113, Folder 1329)
      - Booklet, 1955 Yearbook: Division of Christian Education (Box 114, Folder 1330)
      - Newsletter, Church Vocations Notes, 1950-1952 (Box 114, Folder 1331)
      - Pamphlet, Assumptions and Viewpoints of the General Secretaries regarding the National Council of the Churches in the U.S.A., 1954 (Box 114, Folder 1332)
      - Periodical, National Council Outlook, December 1952-December 1953 (Box 114, Folder 1333)
      - Periodical, National Council Outlook, January 1954-November 1954 (Box 114, Folder 1334)
      - Periodical, National Council Outlook, November 1954-October 1955 (Box 114, Folder 1335)
      - Periodical, National Council Outlook (incomplete run for 1957), November 1955-May 1957 (Box 114, Folder 1336)
  - Student Volunteer Movement for Foreign Missions
    - Conferences
      - 15th Quadrennial Conference, Conference materials, 1947-1948 (Box 114, Folder 1337)
      - 16th Quadrennial Conference, Follow up suggestions, 1951 (Box 114, Folder 1338)
      - 16th Quadrennial Conference, Group leaders seminar, 1951 (Box 114, Folder 1339)
      - 16th Quadrennial Conference, Minutes of various planning committees, 1949-1951 (Box 114, Folder 1340)
      - 16th Quadrennial Conference, Minutes of various planning committees, 1949-1951 (Box 115, Folder 1341)
      - 16th Quadrennial Conference, Planning committee documents, 1951 (Box 115, Folder 1342)
      - 17th Quadrennial, Conference packet including conference newspaper, 1955 (Box 115, Folder #1343)
      - 17th Quadrennial Conference, Correspondence re. planning committee, 1953-1955 (Box 115, Folder 1344)
      - 17th Quadrennial Conference, Directory of the Ecumenical Student Conference on the Christian World Mission, 1955 (Box 115, Folder 1345)
      - 17th Quadrennial Conference, Draft of The Church Re-Thinks Its Mission: a Study Book Compiled and Edited by Keith R. Bridston, 1954 (Box 115, Folder 1346)
      - 17th Quadrennial Conference, Mincon committee, 1955-1956 (Box 115, Folder 1347)
      - 17th Quadrennial Conference, Working committee, 1955-1956 (Box 115, Folder 1348)
      - 17th Quadrennial Conference, Working committee, 1955-1956 (Box 115, Folder 1349)
    - General Records
      - Budget statements, 1954-1956, 1958 (Box 115, Folder 1350)
      - Consultation between USCC and SVM, 1947 (Box 115, Folder 1351)
      - Consultation about merging ISM, SVM, and USCC, 1958 (Box 115, Folder 1352)
      - Correspondence, General, 1947-1951 (Box 116, Folder 1353)
      - Correspondence, General, 1951-1952 (Box 116, Folder 1354)
      - Correspondence, General, 1954-1957 (Box 116, Folder 1355)
      - Draft, "Suggested Study Outline for USCC and SVM Travel Staff for Preparation and Proposed Campus-Centered, Week-End Study Retreat" (Box 116, Folder 1356)
      - Manual for SVM Conference-Centered Campus Visits on the University and the Christian World Mission (Box 116, Folder 1357)
      - Meeting agendas and documents, Board of Directors, 1953-1954 (Box 116, Folder 1358)
      - Meeting agendas and documents, Board of Directors, 1955-1956 (Box 116, Folder 1359)
      - Meeting agendas and documents, Board of Directors, 1957 (Box 116, Folder 1360)
      - Meeting agendas and documents, Board of Directors, 1958 (Box 116, Folder 1361)
      - Meeting agenda and documents, Executive Board: Division of Foreign Missions, 1953 (Box 116, Folder 1362)
      - Meeting agenda and documents, Executive Committee, 1956 (Box 116, Folder 1363)
      - Memos, 1954-1955, 1958 (Box 117, Folder 1364)
      - Minutes, Ad Hoc Committee on Ecumenical Mission Teams, 1956-1957 (Box 117, Folder 1365)
      - Minutes, Advisory Council, 1957 (Box 117, Folder 1366)
      - Minutes, Annual Meeting of the Corporation, 1948, 1950, 1955, 1957 (Box 117, Folder 1367)
      - Minutes, Board of Directors, 1948-1950 (Box 117, Folder 1368)
      - Minutes, Board of Directors, 1950-1952 (Box 117, Folder 1369)
      - Minutes, Board of Directors, 1955-1957 (Box 117, Folder 1370)
      - Minutes, Commission on the Future of the SVM, Committee on Enlistment for Missionary Vocations, and Conference on Christian Frontiers, 1947, 1948, 1957 (Box 117, Folder 1371)
      - Minutes, Executive Committee, 1948-1950 (Box 117, Folder 1372)
      - Minutes, Executive Committee, 1950-1952 (Box 117, Folder 1373)
      - Minutes, Executive Committee, 1952-1955 (Box 118, Folder 1374)
      - Minutes, Executive Committee, 1955-1959 (Box 118, Folder 1375)
      - Minutes, Frontiers Committee, October 25, 1957 (Box 118, Folder 1376)
      - Minutes, Literature Committee, 1949-1956 (Box 118, Folder 1377)
      - Minutes, Nomination Committee, 1955-1956, 1958 (Box 118, Folder 1378)
      - Minutes, Policy Committee, 1952, 1956-1957 (Box 118, Folder 1379)
      - Minutes, Staff minutes, 1955-1957 (Box 118, Folder 1380)
      - Minutes, Student Fellowship Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 118, Folder 1381)
      - Policy Committee documents, 1953-1956 (Box 118, Folder 1382)
      - Reports, including The Student Volunteer Movement within the American Student Christian Movement and Report on the Field Program, 1955, n.d. (Box 118, Folder 1383)
      - SVM--USCC relationship, 195-1954 (Box 118, Folder 1384)
      - Traveling secretary information including documents for briefing conference, 1948, 1957 (Box 118, Folder 1385)
    - Publications and Printed Materials
      - Brochures and flyers, 1946,1951-1958 (Box 118, Folder 1386)